<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<MibreitGallery imagePath="galleries/favorites/images/" thumbPath="galleries/favorites/small/">
<images>
<image>
<filename>Rain-Forest.jpg</filename>
<caption>Cloud Forest</caption>
<alt>Mist and Rain drifts through the cloud forest in the hills of Santa Marta.</alt>
<altDe>Nebel und Regen ziehen durch den Wald in den Hügeln von Santa Marta.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Desert-Nights.jpg</filename>
<caption>Desert Nights</caption>
<alt>The Milky Way over the Erg Chigaga in Morocco on a beautiful night.</alt>
<altDe>Die Milchstraße über der Erg Chigaga in Marokko an einer wunderschönen Nacht.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Essaouira-Surf.jpg</filename>
<caption>Essaouira Surf</caption>
<alt>Waves crashing at the short in front of the Essaouira ramparts</alt>
<altDe>Wellen schlagen an die Küste vor der Stadtmauer von Essaouira.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Stubai-Mountains.jpg</filename>
<caption>Stubai Magic</caption>
<alt>The Mountains of the Stubai Valley and the Rinnensee on a stormy evening.</alt>
<altDe>Die Berge des Stubaitals und der Rinnensee an einem stürmischen Abend.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Fantasia.jpg</filename>
<caption>Fantasia</caption>
<alt>The hills and forests of Saxony Switzerland at Sunrise.</alt>
<altDe>Die Hügel und Wälder der Sächsischen Schweiz zu Sonnenaufgang.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Secret-Beach-Blues.jpg</filename>
<caption>Secret Beach</caption>
<alt>A secluded beach in the South of Mahe Island, the main island of the Seychelles.</alt>
<altDe>Ein versteckter Strand im Süden von Mahe, der Hauptinsel der Seychellen.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Inferno.jpg</filename>
<caption>Inferno - Australia</caption>
<alt>A spectacular sunset at Whisky Bay in Wilsons Promontory National Park in Australia.</alt>
<altDe>Ein spektakulärer Sonnenuntergang an der Whisky Bay im Wilsons Promontory Nationalpark in Australien.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Adraga-Sunset.jpg</filename>
<caption>Adraga Sunset - Portugal</caption>
<alt>Sunset at Praia da Adraga in Portugal.</alt>
<altDe>Sonnenuntergang am Praia da Adraga in Portugal.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Oasis.jpg</filename>
<caption>Oasis - Peru</caption>
<alt>The desert Oasis of Huacachina in Peru during Sunrise.</alt>
<altDe>Die Wüstenoase Huacachina in Peru zu Sonnenaufgang.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Gibson-Steps.jpg</filename>
<caption>Gibson Steps - Australia</caption>
<alt>The Gibson Steps at the 12 Apostels coast in Australia with a colorful sunset behind.</alt>
<altDe>Die Gibson Steps bei den 12 Aposteln in Australien mit einem farbenfrohen Sonnenuntergang.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Auckland-Motorway.jpg</filename>
<caption>Auckland Blues - New Zealand</caption>
<alt>The Auckland Skyline with the motorway as seen during Blue hour in the morning.</alt>
<altDe>Die Skyline Aucklands zur Blauen Stunde am morgen.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Revelation.jpg</filename>
<caption>Revelation - New Zealand</caption>
<alt>Mount Ruapehu and the lower Tama Lake on a windy evening in New Zealand.</alt>
<altDe>Mount Ruapehu und der Lower Tama See an einem windigen Abend in Neuseeland.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Dark-Side-of-the-Moon.jpg</filename>
<caption>Dark Side of the Moon - Chile</caption>
<alt>The bizarre rock formations of the Valle de La Luna in the Atacama in Chile.</alt>
<altDe>Die bizarren Felsformationen des Valle de la Luna in der Atacama in Chile.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>bandon-sun.jpg</filename>
<caption>Bandon Sunset - USA</caption>
<alt>Sunset behind the sea stacks of Bandon Beach in Oregon.</alt>
<altDe>Sonnenuntergang hinter den Sea Stacks des Bandon Beach in Oregon.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Natural-History-Museum.jpg</filename>
<caption>Natural History Museum - London</caption>
<alt>The entrance hall of the Natural History Museum in London.</alt>
<altDe>Die Eingangshalle des Natural History Museums in London.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>mumbles.jpg</filename>
<caption>Bracelet Bay - Wales</caption>
<alt>The Mumbles Lighthouse and Bracelet Bay on the Gower Peninsula in Wales.</alt>
<altDe>Die Bracelet Bay und der Mumbles Leuchtturm auf der Gower Peninsula in Wales.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Grobbach-Rainforest.jpg</filename>
<caption>German Rainforest - Germany</caption>
<alt>The Grobbach river in the lush, green Black Forest at springtime.</alt>
<altDe>Der Grobbach im saftig grünen Schwarzwald im Frühling.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Krimml-Magic.jpg</filename>
<caption>Krimml Magic - Austria</caption>
<alt>The mighty Krimml Waterfall in magical morning light.</alt>
<altDe>Der mächtige Krimmler Wasserfall im magischen Morgenlicht.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Marinha-Dawn.jpg</filename>
<caption>Marinha Dawn - Portugal</caption>
<alt>Praia da Marinha at the Algarve in Portugal during sunrise.</alt>
<altDe>Praia da Marinha an der Algarve in Portugal zu Sonnenaufgang.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Milford-Blues.jpg</filename>
<caption>Milford Blues - New Zealand</caption>
<alt>The fiord and the mountains of Milford Sound at evening.</alt>
<altDe>Die Berge und der Fjord des Milford Sound am Abend.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Rappensee-Sunlight.jpg</filename>
<caption>Rappensee Sunset - Germany</caption>
<alt>Sunset in the Algäu Mountains of Germany.</alt>
<altDe>Sonnenuntergang in den Allgäuer Bergen von Deutschland</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Salt.jpg</filename>
<caption>Salt - Bolivia</caption>
<alt>The salt plains of the Salar de Uyuni in Bolivia.</alt>
<altDe>Die Salzwüste der Salar de Uyuni in Bolivien.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Sonnenspitze.jpg</filename>
<caption>Alpine Paradise - Austria</caption>
<alt>The Sonnespitze Mountain in the Austrian Alps with the Zugspitze.</alt>
<altDe>Die Sonnenspitze in den österreichischen Alpen mit der Zugspitze.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>trotternish.jpg</filename>
<caption>Trotternish - Isle of Skye</caption>
<alt>The Trotternish ridge as seen from the Quiraing during sunrise.</alt>
<altDe>Das Trotternish zu Sonnenaufgang, gesehen vom Quiraing.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Westminster-Storm.jpg</filename>
<caption>Westminster Storm - London</caption>
<alt>Stormy sunset over Westminster Bridge in London.</alt>
<altDe>Ein stürmischer Sonnenuntergang über der Westminster Brücke in London.</altDe>
</image>
<image>
<filename>Yaki-Point.jpg</filename>
<caption>Yaki Point - Grand Canyon</caption>
<alt>Yaki Point at the South Rim of the Grand Canyon in the US.</alt>
<altDe>Yaki Point am Südrand des Grand Canyon in den USA.</altDe>
</image>
</images>
</MibreitGallery>
